Guide to the Santiago Armengod prints MSS.PRINTS.0476
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Santiago Armengod prints
2009-2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Armengod, Santiago
Libros Latinos
MSS PRINTS 0476
2.4 Linear Feet (3 map folders)
Content Description
A collection of relief prints and linoleum block prints by Santiago Armengod (who often uses the pseudonyms Mazatl and Cordyceps), all signed, dated, and numbered by the artist. Most are political and/or activist in theme.
Biographical note
Santiago Armengod is a Mexican artist and activist. He lives in Mexico and is a member of a number of art collectives, including Justseeds and Escuela de Cultura Popular Martires del 68.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Libros Latinos in 2014.
Arrangement
Listed alphabetically.
Armengod, Santiago; Mexico--In art; Mexico--History--Autonomy and independence movements
- El censontle, 2014 (Map-folder 2)
- Control social, 2010 (Map-folder 3)
- Defendamos los sitios sagrados, no a la mineria en Wirikuta, 2012 (Map-folder 3)
- La desesperacion es la materia prima del cambio drastico, 2013 (Map-folder 2)
- El Diablo Anda en Bicicleta, 2013 (Map-folder 2)
  General
  Text on poster reads "Voy con el señor, si no vuelvo estoy con el"
- Don Carlos Chichimecatecuhtli Ometochtzin, 2013 (Map-folder 3)
- Extinction II, 2013 (Map-folder 2)
- Extinction, 2012 (Map-folder 2)
- Extinction 6, 2012 (Map-folder 2)
- ¿Fe?, 2009 (Map-folder 1)
- Hecate I, 2013 (Map-folder 1)
- Hecate II, 2013 (Map-folder 1)
- Kimberly Rivera, 2011 (Map-folder 3)
- Libres Y salvajes, 2013 (Map-folder 1)
- La lucha sigue, 2014 (Map-folder 3)
- Todavia tenemos tiempo, 2011 (Map-folder 3)
- YYA INU CHU'MA, 2010 (Map-folder 1)
- Zapata vive, 2013 (Map-folder 1)